Guide to the Records of Amnesty International of the USA, Inc.
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VII: Campaign and Country Files, 1972-1997
  - Subseries VII.2: Country Campaigns and Country Files, 1972-1997
    The records include files on both countries and country-related campaigns and actions undertaken by Amnesty International. The campaign records include background materials, clippings, correspondence, mailings with information and instructions for AIUSA groups, meeting notes and reports, memoranda, news releases, planning materials, recommended actions, reports, updates, and urgent actions.
    - AI Campaigning: A Strategy for the Future, 1991 (Box ###, Folder 14)
    - Definitions of Campaigns and Special Actions, 1979 (Box ###, Folder 15)
    - Africa
      - Academics and Students Who are Prisoners of Conscience (POCs), 1990-1991 (Box ###, Folder 16)
      - Africa Charter Action, 1991 (Box ###, Folder 17)
        (Strategy Meetings, International Secretariat (IS) documents, etc.)
      - Campaign Against Disappearances and Political Killings, 1993 (Box ###, Folder 18)
      - Death Penalty Action, 1991 (Box ###, Folder 19)
      - Human Rights Monitors Action, 1994 (Box ###, Folder 20)
      - Algeria--Prisoners of Conscience (POCs)--Group Level Action on, 1986 (Box ###, Folder 21)
      - Benin--Group Level Action, 1987 (Box ###, Folder 22)
      - Burundi
        - Section Level Action, 1992 (Box ###, Folder 23)
        - Burundi Crisis, 1994-1995 (Box ###, Folder 24)
      - Chad (Box 300)
        - Group Level Action, 1986 (Box 300, Folder 1)
        - Limited Campaign, 1993 (Box 300, Folder 2)
          (Includes Chad: Never Again? Photograph display)
        - Limited Campaign, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 300, Folder 3-4)
      - Ethiopia
        - 1976-1977 (Box 300, Folder 5)
          (reports and statements by Dr. Arnt K. Meyer-Lie)
        - Group-Level Action, 1986 (Box 300, Folder 6)
      - Guinea--Campaign and Group-Level Action on Disappearances, 1982, (2 Folders) (Box 300, Folder 7-8)
        [FOLDER 8 IS restricted until 2057]
      - Malawi--Group-Level Action, 1992 (Box 300, Folder 9)
      - Mauritania--Group-Level Action, 1990 (Box 300, Folder 10)
      - Namibia
        - Special Action, 1982 (Box 300, Folder 11)
          (See also files on South Africa)
        - Campaign to Abolish Torture (CAT), 1985
          - AI Statements on Torture In (Box 300, Folder 12)
          - Campaign Strategy Planning (Box 300, Folder 13)
          - Correspondence (Box 300, Folder 14)
          - Correspondence/Mailing (Box 300, Folder 15)
          - News Clippings (Box 300, Folder 16)
      - Rwanda
        - Rwanda Crisis, 1994 (Box 300, Folder 17)
        - Rwanda Mission Project, 1994 (Box 300, Folder 18)
      - South Africa (Box 301)
        - South Africa/Namibia Special Action, 1982 (Box 301, Folder 1)
          (See also files on Namibia)
        - Campaign, 1986
          - AIUSA Testimony, South Africa: Human Rights Violations Under the State of Emergency (Box 301, Folder 2)
            (Submitted to the United States Senate Foreign Relations Committee)
          - AI Circulars--#1A, 1B, 2, 7A, 8 (Box 301, Folder 3)
          - Follow-up (Box 301, Folder 4)
          - General, (2 Folders) (Box 301, Folder 5-6)
          - Health Network Mailing (Box 301, Folder 7)
          - Mailings (Box 301)
          - #1, 3, 4, (3 Folders) (Box 301, Folder 8-10)
          - #5 (Box 301, Folder 11)
          - #6, 7, (2 Folders) (Box 301, Folder 12-13)
          - Special Mailings (Box 301, Folder 14)
          - Updates--#2, 3, 4, 6 (Box 301, Folder 15)
        - Country Action, 1989, (2 Folders) (Box 301, Folder 16-17)
        - Section-Level Action, 1992 (Box 301, Folder 18-19)
      - Sudan
        - Country Action, 1990 (Box 301, Folder 20)
        - Campaign
          - 1992 (Box 301, Folder 21)
          - General, 1995, (3 Folders) (Box 301, Folder 22-24)
          - Press Packet, 1995 (Box 301, Folder 25)
          - Sign-Up Sheets, 1995 (Box 301, Folder 26)
            (For AIUSA Groups)
      - Uganda (Box 302)
        - Special Action, 1982 (Box 302, Folder 1-2)
        - Campaign to Abolish Torture (CAT), 1985 (Box 302, Folder 3)
        - Country Action, 1992
          - AI Documents (Box 302, Folder 4)
          - Evaluations (Box 302, Folder 5)
          - General [restricted until 2067] (Box 302, Folder 6)
          - Mailings--#1, 2, 3 and Campaign Updates #2, 3 (Box 302, Folder 7)
          - Media (Box 302, Folder 8)
          - Recommended Actions for Sections and Groups (Box 302, Folder 9)
          - Sign-Ups (Box 302, Folder 10)
          - Strategy Meeting and Other Materials (Box 302, Folder 11)
      - Zaire
        - Campaign, 1980 (Box 302, Folder 12)
        - Campaign and Follow-up Action, 1980, (2 Folders) (Box 302, Folder 13-14)
        - 1980-1983 (Box 302, Folder 15)
        - Campaign to Abolish Torture (CAT), 1984-1985 (Box 302, Folder 16-17)
      - Zimbabwe, 1978-1979 (Box 302, Folder 18)
        (Rhodesia)
    - Americas
      - Campaign Against Disappearances and Political Killings, 1993 (Box 302, Folder 19)
      - Argentina--Campaign, 1978 (Box 302, Folder 20)
      - Brazil
        - 1973 (Box 302, Folder 21)
          (Contains Report on Allegations of Torture in Brazil by Amnesty International)Campaign, 1988-1989
          - Circulars #1-7, 10-11 (Box 302, Folder 22)
          - General (Box 302, Folder 23)
          - Mailings #1-8 and Other Materials, (6 Folders) (Box 302, Folder 24-29)
        - Extended Group-Level Action on Torture and Extrajudicial Executions, 1990 (Box 302, Folder 30)
      - Chile (Box 303)
        - Special Action
          - 1981 (Box 303, Folder 1)
          - 1983 (Box 303, Folder 2)
            (Includes report on the Washington Component of the Chile Special Action)
        - Campaign to Abolish Torture (CAT), 1984-1985 (Box 303, Folder 3)
        - Campaign, 1986
          - Activities of AIUSA Local Groups (Box 303, Folder 4)
          - Bank of America (Box 303, Folder 5)
          - Barnes, Ambassador Harry (Box 303, Folder 6)
          - Billboards (Box 303, Folder 7)
          - Cartoons--Selection from Hoy Magazine (Box 303, Folder 8)
            (Cartoon captions are in Spanish)
          - Chilean Ambassador Herman Errazuriz (Box 303, Folder 9)
          - Chile/Sri Lanka Campaign Memos (Box 303, Folder 10)
          - Circulars #1-11 (Box 303, Folder 11)
          - Esmeralda (ship)--Clippings and Correspondence (Box 303, Folder 12)
          - Evaluation of (Box 303, Folder 13)
          - General, (4 Folders) (Box 303, Folder 14-17)
          - Kellogg Institute (University of Notre Dame, Illinois) (Box 303, Folder 18)
          - Loans to Chile (Box 303, Folder 19)
            (Includes Congressional hearings, statements, clippings, meeting notes, etc.)
          - Mailings and Updates (Box 303, Folder 20)
          - Meetings with Outside Corporations (Organizations) (Box 303, Folder 21)
          - Miscellaneous Press Clippings on Chile (Box 303, Folder 22)
          - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company (Box 303, Folder 23)
          - News from AI Groups during the Chile Campaign (Box Box 305, Folder 1)
          - Planning (Box 305, Folder 2)
            (Includes both the Sri Lanka and Chile Campaigns)
          - Planning for AI Groups During the Chile Campaign (Box 305, Folder 3)
            (Includes both the Chile and Sri Lanka Campaigns)
          - Related Organizations and Documents for the Chile Campaign (Box 305, Folder 4)
          - Religious Groups (Box 305, Folder 5)
          - Rojas, Rodrigo and Carmen Quintana--Burning of (Box 305, Folder 6)
            (Includes Rojas Fund)
          - Targeted Companies and Banks (Box 305, Folder 7)
          - United States/Chile Military Connections (Box 305, Folder 8)
          - United States Corporate Activity in Chile, (2 Folders) (Box 305, Folder 9-10)
          - United States Government (Box 305, Folder 11)
          - Veronica De Negri Tour, 1986 (Box 305, Folder 12)
        - Disappearances Campaign, 1988
          - Asi Lo Hemos Vivido (This is Our Story) (Box 305, Folder 13)
            (AI Circular and 15 drawing by relatives of the disappeared to be used as a visual display)
          - Circulars (Box 305, Folder 14)
          - Disappearances in Chile: Images of the Search (Box 305, Folder 15)
            (Compiled by Amnesty International)
          - General (Box 305, Folder 16)
            (Includes background information, campaign organization materials, clippings, etc.)
      - Columbia (Box 306)
        - Campaign, 1988
          - General (Box 306, Folder 1)
          - Mailing #1-5 and Follow-Up, (5 Folders) (Box 306, Folder 2-6)
          - Renault/Columbia (Box 306, Folder 7)
        - Campaign--General, 1989 (Box 306, Folder 8)
          (Includes information on country action)
        - Campaign Against Disappearances and Political Killings, 1993-1994
          - Address Lists for Appeals (Box 306, Folder 9)
          - Correspondence sent to Columbia, Board Mailings Re: Campaign, Statement by AIUSA Executive Director William Shulz, etc. (Box 306, Folder 10)
          - Lives Behind the Lies Campaign
            - Evaluation and Reporting Forms (Box 306, Folder 11)
              (Includes correspondence)
            - General, (4 Folders) (Box 306, Folder 12-15)
          - International Secretariat (IS) Docs (Box 306, Folder 16)
          - Legal Support Network
            - Mailings to (Box 306, Folder 17)
            - Packet mailed to Bar Association interested in participating in the action (Box 306, Folder 18)
          - Media Strategy (Box 306, Folder 19)
          - Packet (Box 306, Folder 20)
          - Petitions/Advertisements to be published in Columbia (Box 306, Folder 21)
          - Press Launch (Box Box 307, Folder 1)
            [restricted until 2025]
          - Sign-Up Sheets (Box 307, Folder 2)
          - Strategy (Box 307, Folder 3)
          - Student Packet (Box 307, Folder 4)
      - El Salvador
        - 1982-1983 (Box 307, Folder 5)
        - Country Action, 1990-1991, (2 Folders) (Box 307, Folder 6-7)
      - Guatemala
        - Central American Special Action (CASA), 1978-1987, (2 Folders) (Box 307, Folder .8-9)
        - Special Action, 1981-1983 (Box 307, Folder 10)
          (Corporation Strategy)
        - Campaign, 1987 (Box 307, Folder 11)
        - Country Action, 1989 (Box 307, Folder 12)
      - Haiti
        - Campaign, 1985
          - Agenda/Minutes/Strategy (Box 307, Folder 13)
          - Drafts and Reports (Box 307, Folder 14)
          - Evaluations of (Box 307, Folder 15)
          - General, (2 Folders) (Box 307, Folder 16-17)
          - Mailings/Memos (Box 307, Folder 18)
        - Crisis Response, 1994, (2 Folders) (Box 307, Folder 19-20)
      - Mexico (Box 308)
        - Special Action on Torture, 1991
          - General, (3 Folders) (Box 308, Folder 1-3)
          - Mailings #1-4 (Box 308, Folder 4)
          - Mexico Motiffs (Box 308, Folder 5)
            (Design Motiffs)
          - PR Coverage (Box 308, Folder 6)
            (Includes newspaper clippings and press releases)
          - PR Pieces (Box 308, Folder 7)
            (Includes news clippings, drafts of brochures, and correspondence )
        - Country Action, 1992-1993 (Box 308, Folder 8)
      - Nicaragua, 1982 (Box 308, Folder 9)
      - Paraguay
        - Campaign, 1977-1978 (Box 308, Folder 10)
        - Country Action, 1989-1990 (Box 308, Folder 11)
      - Peru
        - Campaign, 1985
          - Correspondence (Box 308, Folder 12)
          - Evaluations of (Box 308, Folder 13)
          - General, (2 Folders) (Box 308, Folder 14-15)
        - Country Action, 1989-1990
          - General, (2 Folders) (Box 308, Folder 16-17)
          - Mailings #1-2 and Final Mailing (Box 308, Folder 18)
        - Campaign, 1991-1992 (Box 308, Folder 19)
      - Uruguay--Campaign, 1976 (Box 308, Folder 20)
    - Asia (Box 309)
      - Campaign Against Disappearances and Political Killings, 1993 (Box 309, Folder 1)
      - Afghanistan
        - Campaign To Abolish Torture (CAT), 1984-1985 (Box 309, Folder 2)
        - Campaign, 1986-1987
          - Circulars #1-3 (Box 309, Folder 3)
          - Correspondence (Box 309, Folder 4)
          - General, (4 Folders) (Box 309, Folder 5-8)
          - Mailings #1-2 (Box 309, Folder 9)
          - Petitions (Box 309, Folder 10)
          - Primer on the Afghanistan Crisis (Box 309, Folder 11)
            (Drafts)
          - Press (Box 309, Folder 12)
        - Campaign and Group-Level Action, 1986-1992 (Box 309, Folder 13)
      - Bangladesh--Campaign (Box 309, Folder 14)
        (Includes mission report)
      - Burma (Myanmar)
        - Group-Level and SEAMRAN (Southeast Asia Mainland Regional Action Network) Campaign, 1988 (Box 309, Folder 15)
        - Campaign, 1990-1991 (Box 309, Folder 16)
        - Student Campaign, 1996 (Box 309, Folder 17)
      - Cambodia (Kampuchea)
        - Campaign, 1987
          - Antiwar Project (Box 309, Folder 18)
            (Mostly form letters)
          - Circulars #1-2 (Box 19)
          - General (Box 309, Folder 20-22)
          - Mailings (Box Box 311, Folder 1)
          - Press Conference of May 29, 1987 (Box 311, Folder 2)
            (Includes press reaction to campaign, memos, statements, reports, etc.)
          - Press (Box 311, Folder 3)
          - Relief Groups (Box 311, Folder 4)
          - Strategy/Planning, (2 Folders) (Box 311, Folder 5-6)
      - China and Tibet
        - Death Penalty Group-Level Action, 1982 (Box 311, Folder 7)
        - Special Action, 1984
          - Evaluations (Box 311, Folder 8)
          - General, (2 Folders) (Box 311, Folder 9-10)
        - Special Appeal for Catholic Prisoners of Conscience (POCs), 1985 (Box 311, Folder 11)
        - Action, 1987
          - Authorities List and Other Materials (Box 311, Folder 12)
          - Businesses and Individuals (Box 311, Folder 13)
          - General, (2 Folders) (Box 311, Folder 14-15)
          - Mailings (Box 311, Folder 16)
        - Emergency Action, 1989
          - (2 Folders) (Box 311, Folder 17, 19)
        - Group-Level Action, 1990 (Box 311, Folder 20)
        - Photo exhibit proposal, 1990 (Box 311, Folder 21)
        - Section-Level, Group-Level, RAN actions, 1991 (Box 311, Folder 22)
          [restricted until 2022]
        - China/Tibet Country Action, 1992 (Box 312)
          - Background and Other Documents (Box 312, Folder 1)
          - Evaluations of (Box 312, Folder 2)
          - Feature Cases (Box 312, Folder 3)
          - General (Box 312, Folder 4)
            (Includes prisoner profiles)
          - Local Group Actions (Box 312, Folder 5)
          - Mailings #1-5, (2 Folders) (Box 312, Folder 6-7)
          - Sign-Up Sheets (Box 312, Folder 8)
          - Strategy (Box 312, Folder 9)
          - Student Material (Box 312, Folder 10)
        - Torture in--CHIRAN and Group-Level action, 1993 (Box 312, Folder 11)
        - Demonstration April 14, 1994 and documents re human rights violations (Box 312, Folder 12)
        - Crisis Response 1994 Re: "1989" prisoners and MFN (Most Favored Nation Trade Status) (Box 312, Folder 13)
        - Tibet--Action against torture in, 1994 (Box 312, Folder 14)
        - Campaign--Strategy Meeting and Schedule, 1995-1996 (Box 312, Folder 15)
      - India
        - Special Action, 1980 (Box 312, Folder 16)
        - Campaign, 1992
          - General (Box 312, Folder 17)
          - Packet (Box 312, Folder 18)
        - Campaign, 1996 (Box 312, Folder 19)
      - Indonesia and East Timor
        - East Timor Campaign, 1985
          - Billboards (Box 312, Folder 20)
          - Campaign Strategy and General Materials, (2 Folders) (Box 312, Folder 21-22)
          - Circulars (Box 312, Folder 23)
          - Clips and Other Material (Box 312, Folder 24)
          - General (Box Box 313, Folder 1)
          - Incoming Letters (Box 313, Folder 2)
          - Mailing Lists (Box 313, Folder 3)
          - Mailings (Box 313, Folder 4)
          - Mailings/Memos (Box 313, Folder 6)
          - United States Senate/House East Timor Correspondence (Box 313, Folder 6)
        - Indonesia Country Action, 1993 (Box 313, Folder 7)
        - Campaign--Action Packet, 1995 (Box 313, Folder 8)
      - Korea, South (South Korea)
        - Campaign, 1981
          - Background (Box 313, Folder 9)
          - Contacts (Box 313, Folder 10)
          - Group Mailings (Box 313, Folder 11)
        - Group Level Action, 1986 (Box 313, Folder 12)
        - Campaign, 1987-1988, (8 Folders)
          - Circulars and Mailings (Box 313, Folder 13)
          - Correspondence (Box 313, Folder 14)
          - Final Report (Box 313, Folder 15)
          - General, (4 Folders) (Box 313, Folder 16-19)
          - Newspaper Clippings (Box 313, Folder 20)
        - Extended Group-Level Action, 1990 (Box 313, Folder 21)
        - Group-Level Action, 1991 (Box 313, Folder 22)
      - Malaysia, 1979-1981 (Box 313, Folder 23)
      - Pakistan (Box 314)
        - Campaign, 1977 (Box 314, Folder 1)
        - Special Action
          - 1980-1981, (2 Folders) (Box 314, Folder 2-3)
          - 1982 (Box 314, Folder 4)
        - Fair Trial Campaign
          - Circulars #1-7 (Box 314, Folder 5)
          - General (Box 314, Folder 6)
      - Philippines
        - Campaign, 1982-1983
          - Campaign Document (Box 314, Folder 7)
          - Campaign Files (Box 314, Folder 8)
            (Includes campaign calendar)
          - Churches (Box 314, Folder 9)
          - Circulars #1, 3 and 4 (Box 314, Folder 10)
          - D.C. Plans (Box 314, Folder 11)
          - Evaluation of (Box 314, Folder 12)
          - General, (2 Folders) (Box 314, Folder 13-14)
          - Group Mailings (Box 314, Folder 15)
          - Miscellaneous Contacts (Box 314, Folder 16)
          - Mission Report (Box 314, Folder 17)
          - Poster Printing (Box 314, Folder 18)
          - Regional Office Plans (Box 314, Folder 19)
          - Trade Unionists (Box 314, Folder 20)
        - Limited Campaign, 1992 (Box 314, Folder 21)
      - Sri Lanka (Box 315)
        - Disappearances Campaign, 1986
          - Campaign Planning and General (Box 315, Folder 1)
          - Circulars #1-5 and Updates #1-5 (Box 315, Folder 2)
          - Correspondence (Box 315, Folder 3)
          - Evaluation of (Box 315, Folder 4)
          - Final Memo (Box 315, Folder 5)
          - General, (3 Folders) (Box 315, Folder 6-8)
          - Jendrzejczyk, Mike (AI Campaign Director)--Remarks at Sri Lankan Union (USA) Conference (Box 315, Folder 9)
          - Mailings (Box 315, Folder 10)
          - Press and Billboard Plans (Box 315, Folder 11)
          - Sign Ups (Box 315, Folder 12)
          - Sri Lanka Union Program in New York City and Other Materials (Box 315, Folder 13)
          - United States Congress (Box 315, Folder 14)
        - Disappearances Group--Level Action, 1987 (Box 315, Folder 15)
        - Campaign, 1990
          - General (Box 315, Folder 16)
          - Mailing #1, #2 and Final Mailing (Box 315, Folder 17)
        - 1993 (Box 315, Folder 18)
          (Might be related to a country action)
      - Thailand--Group Level Action, 1987 (Box 315, Folder 19)
      - Vietnam
        - Group Level Action
          - 1983 (Box 315, Folder 20)
            (Circular #1, only)
          - 1990 (Box 315, Folder 315 type="Folder" label="Folder">21)
    - Europe (Box 316)
      - Campaign Against Disappearances and Political Killings, 1993 (Box 316, Folder 1)
      - Albania, 1996 (Box 316, Folder 2)
      - Austria--Group-Level Action and WERAN Action, 1990 (Box 316, Folder 3)
      - Chechen Republic--Section-Level Action, 1995 (Box 316, Folder 4)
      - Czechoslovakia--Campaign, 1987 (Box 316, Folder 5)
      - East Germany--Special Action, 1981 (Box 316, Folder 6)
      - Greece--Group-Level Action, 1986 and 1988 (Box 316, Folder 7)
      - Italy--Group-Level Action, 1986 (Box 316, Folder 8)
      - Poland--Special Action on Internment, 1981 (Box 316, Folder 9)
      - Turkey
        - Group-Level Action, 1983 (Box 316, Folder 10)
        - Campaign To Abolish Torture (CAT), 1984 (Box 316, Folder 11)
        - Group-Level Action
          - 1985 (Box 316, Folder 12)
          - 1987 (Box 316, Folder 13)
        - 1987-1990 (Box 316, Folder 14)
        - Campaign, 1988-1989
          - Circulars (Box 316, Folder 15)
          - General, (4 Folders) (Box 316, Folder 16-19)
          - Mailings #1-3 and Final Mailing (Box 316, Folder 20)
          - Preliminary Summary Of (Box 316, Folder 21)
        - Group-Level Action, 1990 (Box 316, Folder 22)
        - Country Action, 1991
          - General (Box 316, Folder 23)
          - Sign Up Sheets (Box 316, Folder 24)
        - Section-Level Action, 1992 (Box 316, Folder 25)
        - Student Special Action, 1994 (Box 316, Folder 26)
        - Campaign, 1996 (Box 316, Folder 27)
      - USSR
        - Campaign To Abolish Torture (CAT), 1985
          - Campaign Plans (Box 316, Folder 28)
          - Clips and Other Materials (Box 316, Folder 29)
          - Correspondence (Box 316, Folder 30)
          - Davydov, Viktor--Re: Psychiatric Abuse (Box 316, Folder 31)
          - General (Box 316, Folder 32)
          - General, (2 Folders) (Box 317, Folder 1-2)
          - Group Evaluations (Box 317, Folder 3)
          - Mailings (Box 317, Folder 4)
            (Includes material related to Anatoly Koryagin)
          - Notes on Meetings (Box 317, Folder 5)
          - Planning Strategy (Box 317, Folder 6)
          - To Read (Box 317, Folder 7)
          - USSR Coordinators Meeting (Box 317, Folder 8)
        - Group-Level Action on death penalty in, 1988 (Box 317, Folder 9)
        - Country Action, 1989, (2 Folders) (Box 317, Folder 10-11)
        - United Kingdom
          (Includes Northern Ireland)Country Action, 1991
          - Action Packet (Box 317, Folder 12)
          - General, (2 Folders) (Box 317, Folder 13-14)
          - Sign Up Sheets (Box 317, Folder 15)
            (for local groups)
      - Yugoslavia
        - Special Action, 1981-1982 (Box 317, Folder 16)
        - Campaign, 1985 (Box 317, Folder 17)
        - Group-Level Action, 1986 (Box 317, Folder 18)
        - Priority Action on Disappearances and Missing Persons, 1995 (Box 317, Folder 19)
    - Middle East and North Africa
      - Egypt
        - Special Action, 1983
          - (General) (Box 317, Folder 20)
          - Local Groups (Box 317, Folder 21)
        - Campaign To Abolish Torture (CAT), 1985 (Box 317, Folder 22)
        - Section-Level Action, 1991-1992 (Box 317, Folder 23)
        - Country Action, 1991-1992 (Box 317, Folder 24)
        - Country Action, 1993 (Box 317, Folder 25)
      - Iran
        - Campaign, 1987
          - Ads (Box 317, Folder 26)
          - Ads and General Materials (Box 317, Folder 27)
          - General, (2 Folders) (Box 317, Folder 28-29)
          - Legal Support Network (LSN) Mailing (Box 319, Folder 1)
          - Mailings #1-5 (Box 319, Folder 2)
          - Newspaper Clippings (Box 319, Folder 3)
          - Planning and Miscellaneous (Box 319, Folder 4)
          - Press (Box 319, Folder 5)
          - Special Action Letter to the Editor (Box 319, Folder 6)
        - Country Action, 1990-1991 (Box 319, Folder 7)
      - Iraq--Group-Level/MERAN (Middle East Regional Action Network) Action, 1989 (Box 319, Folder 8)
      - Israel and the Occupied Territories
        - Updates to Administrative Detention During the Palestinian Intifada (MDE 15/41/89 and 15/42/89) (Box 319, Folder 9)
        - Campaign, 1991 (Box 319, Folder 10)
        - Military justice, 1991 (Box 319, Folder 11)
      - Morocco
        - Special Action, 1982 (Box 319, Folder 12)